SPC Matthew Levandowski

¡Removed From WEB Version; Allendale, MI 49401-8142 ¡Removed From Web Version; levandowski.matthew@gmail.com http://www2.gvsu.edu/~levandma/

Objective

Experienced military leader with documented success in responsible and challenging positions; seeking a position to gain work related experience in order to progress to higher level positions. I have a proven record of accomplishment, mission-critical decision making, time-management, and extensive teamwork abilities; with the ability to develop and implement effective action plans. I have fulfilled a tour of duty in Afghanistan and four years of military service with an honorable discharge.

Education

Grand Valley State University

Allendale, MI

B.A.Sc., Information Systems (Grades: 80%)

Sep. 2009 - Present

 Relevant courses: Java programming, Data Structures and Algorithms, Digital Design, Computer Architecture

Muskegon Community College

Muskegon, MI

2001-2006

A.S.A., Science and Arts

- Finished degree after completing 4 year Active Duty contract with the U.S. Army.
- Relevant courses: Physics, Calculus, Statistics, Electroacoustic music

Work Experience

180th Transportation Co., U.S. Army Reserve

Muskegon, MI

25F Communication Specialist

Aug 2009 - Aug. 2010

- Train on various soldier skills and wheeled truck driving. Plan and execute regular training exercises in support of the 180th Transportation Company.

Kohls Department Store

Muskegon, MI

Advertisement Setter

Nov 2009 - Present

 Work with other associates as a team to inventory and assess advertisement pricing and policies for entire store. Assist customers and perform customer service tasks.

Shareco Communications

Grand Rapids, MI

 $Telecommunications\ Line\ Installer$

Mar. 2008 - Nov. 2008

- I was responsible for the installation, repair, and termination of cabling in commercial and residential business.
- Proficient in the use of CAT5E, CAT6, 100-pair copper wire, and standard RG5 coaxial cable.
- Installation and splicing of fiber optic lines in commercial settings.

710 BSB, 3rd BCT, 10th MTN DIV, U.S. Army

Afghanistan

Communications Specialist OEF VII

Feb. 2006 - Jul. 2007

- Deployed in support of Operation Enduring Freedom as a communication specialist for a company sized element with more than 150 employees.
- Participated in the Joint Task Force as security for the occupying NATO and ISAF forces.

- Participated in the successful repatriation of a US Soldier in a Search and Rescue Mission.
- Maintained and Installed radio communication and navigation devices in armored vehicles.

10th Mountain Division, U.S. Army

Fort Drum, NY

25F Network Switching Systems Operator / Maintainer

Aug. 2005 - Feb. 2006

- Directly responsible for the installation, maintenance, and repair of over half a million dollars of communication equipment for a company with over 150 soldiers.
- Participated in successful training at JROTC in Fort Polk, Louisiana.
- Conducted numerous training exercises successfully in light infantry.

Military Awards

Joint Service Achievement Medal (Secretary of Defense)	May 2007
ISAF Medal Afghanistan (NATO)	2007
Joint Meritorious Unit Award (CJTF-76)	2007
Army Commendation Medal (U.S. Army)	2007
Army Good Conduct Medal (x2) (U.S. Army)	2007
Army Certification of Achievement (U.S. Army)	2006

Security Clearance

Secret (US Army) Exp. 2012

Skills

Programming: Java, HTML, CSS, BASH, Perl

Operating Systems: Linux (Debian, Gentoo, ArchLinux), Solaris, UNIX, Windows 95/98/NT/2000/XP/VISTA/WIN 7

Applications: Vim, Eclipse, LATEX, OpenOffice, MS Office 2007, Adobe Photoshop/Premiere

Military Skills: General Dynamics C4 - MSE Network Systems, COMTECH MTS, Plugr, and BlueForce Tracker GPS devices, COMSEC devices, SIPR and NIPR networks, SINCGARS Radios, SMART-T Satellite Communications, Cisco routers

Miscellaneous: software configuration management, strong verbal and written communication skills, excellent troubleshooting skills, exceptional problem solving skills, good teams skills

Interests

Academic: RF/wireless, Operating Systems design / maintenance, Computer Security, Information Assurance

Sports: Playing soccer and Running

Computers: Enjoy using and learning Linux systems, Repairing computers and electronics at home and for friends, and writing JAVA software

Musical: Playing guitar and midi keyboard

Memberships: Student Veteran Organization, CS Study Group, Total Trek Quest

Other: Reading novels